Office of Physical Planning Records, 1869-1994 (bulk 1946-1994): Finding Aid AC154
University Archives
- Series 3: Architectural Drawings (Oversized), 1893-1993; 6 boxes; 212 folders
  - Dodge Memorial Gate. Proposed, dates not examined; 1 folder Drawings for various sites: Between Henry and 1901 - elevations, renderings and reproductions of renderings from the North, undated; elevation from North and South June 11, 1931. Between Henry and Foulke; McCosh walk near Washington Road - green and orange pencil and red crayon rendering, dated December 2, 1932. Between Hamilton and Joline - drawings December 12, 1932 street elevation; December 19, 1932 schemes B & C; green and orange pencil, reproduct ion of rendering scheme C, December 22, 1932 (Folder Oversize folder 178)
  - Dodge Memorial Gate, dates not examined; 1 folder Drawing for final gate; 6 sheets of drawings dated December 19, 1932 - May 31, 1933; 1 undated reproduction of rendering (Folder Oversize folder 180)
  - Dodge Memorial Gate and Eisenhart Arch, dates not examined; 1 folder 20 drawings and reproductions (Folder Oversize folder 181)
    Trautwein and Howard.
  - Dodge Memorial Gate and Eisenhart Arch, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 182)
    Miscellaneous; Arms of James Arriere, Dodge Gate, dated October 7, 1932.
  - Fitzrandolph Gates, dates not examined; 1 folder 2 reproductions undated; 1 reproduction dated January 6, 1905 (Folder Oversize folder 183)
  - Fitzrandolph Gates, dates not examined; 1 folder Site plan dated January 1904 and revised May 31 (Folder Oversize folder 184)
  - Rolled transparencies of Dodge Memorial Gate, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 106)
    Purchase Order 3109. Indiana Limestone Company.
    Item is torn.
  - Elevation Drawings of McCosh Hall, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 211)
    Panoramic drawings to be stored at Firestone Library.
  - Photograph of Rendering of Arch at end of College Road, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 107)
  - Drawings, Sketches and Cutouts for Bronze Tigers Between Whig and Clio Halls, 1968-1969; Moore, Bruce; 1 box (Folder Oversize folder 187, Box 104)
  - 20 Surveys and Plans of Campus and Surroundings, and Plan of Palmer Stadium, 1906-1971; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 188)
  - Township Atlas and Borough Tax Map, 1985; 1993; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 189)
  - Campus Maps and Plans used for Various Projects; Includes Maps of Student Housing Distribution by Race, Sex, Year, etc, 1962-1976; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 190)
  - Maps of Princeton-area tracts of land, 1900-1916; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 191)
    AR.2017.079
    Seven maps of Princeton-area tracts of land that were of interest to the University, including the Prospect and Gray Farm tracts and Bayle's Farm. Maps detail proposed streets and lots, and most were surveyed by Henry A. Harris or C.S. Sincerbeaux.
  - Building for I.D.A. (Sketches and Plans), 1959; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 192)
  - Preliminary Plan of Proposed Subdivision of Property of Princeton University, 1956; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 210)
    Dean Mathey property. Drawn by Edward Van Note.
  - Campus Projects 1988-2002, Undated; 1 box (Box 105)
    AR-2019-103
  - Olmsted Campus Plan, 1893; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 212)
    To be stored at Firestone Library.